const Caste = [
	{
		questionText: 'History of Caste in India',
		ans: ['S.V Ketkar'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Caste and Race in India',
		ans: ['GS Ghurye'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The People of India',
		ans: ['Herbet Risley'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Social Changes In Moderate In India',
		ans: ['MN Srinivas'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Indian Villages',
		ans: ['MN Srinivas'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Caste in Modern India and other Essays',
		ans: ['MN Srinivas'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The  Culture and Civilzation of Modern India',
		ans: ['DD Kosambi'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Anhiliation of Caste',
		ans: ['BR Ambedkar'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Caste is a closed group',
		ans: ['Majjundar and Madan'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Caste is a Collection of familes, bearing common name, clamming a common decent, homogeneous community',
		ans: ['Risley'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Tradition /Divine Theory',
		ans: ['Rigveda'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Racial Theory',
		ans: ['Herbet Risley'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Occupational Theory',
		ans: ['Nesfield'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Brahmanical or political theory',
		ans: ['Abbe Dubois & Dr. Ghurye'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Geographical Theory',
		ans: ['Gibert'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Theory of Cultural Integration',
		ans: ['Sarath Chandra Roy'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Evolution Theory',
		ans: [' Denzillb bestson'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Theory of Mana',
		ans: ['Hutton'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Guild Theory',
		ans: ['Denzil Ibbestson'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Religious or Samskar Theory',
		ans: ['Hocrt & Emile Senart'],
	},
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },

];

export default Caste;
